

CHRISTOPHER GOODFELLOW

JUNIOR FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a Full Stack Software Development student with, particularly strong frontend development skills. A passion for coding has led me to undertake Code Institute's Diploma in Software Development with the aim of pursuing a full-time career in this field. Upon the completion of this course, I will have delivered four progressively technical websites using newly learnt techniques and skills. With nearly three years of professional experience in the finance sector, I have demonstratable expertise in working efficiently to solve problems and hit targets. Combined with nearly five years in hospitality delivering exceptional customer experience, I look forward to embarking on a new challenge within Software Development.

CONTACT DETAILS

(Mobile: 07801 994 199

chrisgoodfellow1@hotmail.com

https://github.com/Tawnygoody



TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Python Flask / Django
- MongoDB
- Version Control (GIT)
- GitHub
- Bootstrap

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Strong numerical and analytical skills.
- Pragmatic approach to problem-solving.
- Proven ability to manage workload to meet deadlines and hit targets.
- Resilience to persevere with tasks until completion.
- Open to learning to gain new knowledge and learn new ways of doing things.
- Quality orientated by checking work for errors to ensure accuracy.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

DATA GATHERER

Virgin Money

January 2020 - February 2021

- Start to end processes are carried out on the in house database system to
 collate a meaningful report of data covering a full record of a customer's
 accounts and products held with the Bank.
- Review and comply with up to date releases, processes and current GDPR legislation's in place.
- Cross referencing and cataloguing data from various 3rd party sources into a standardised format, allowing investigation handlers to make informed decisions, on all customer products.
- Identifying vulnerable customers using SQL within various databases, in order to prioritise workload.
- Ensuring personal performance quality stays above 90%, whilst meeting productivity targets.

CLAIMS HANDLER

Clydesdale & Yorkshire Banking Group

July 2018 - January 2020

- Processing customer data provided by a client, or Claims Management Company (CMC), into a suitable format to provide information relating to Personal Protection Insurance (PPI).
- Cross reference data across a range of systems in order to highlight additional information relating to the client, and confirm ownership of accounts.
- Working with Robotic Process Automation to maximise efficiency and increase output.
- Request third party information that has not been digitised to provide the customer with the most accurate outcome.
- Consulting with CYBG call centre's to aid in providing information relating to a clients request.
- Co-operate with CMC's to resolve any disputes they may have in relation to their clients' request.
- Following process guides & maps ensuring personal performance quality stays above 90% whilst also meeting team targets.
- Working with the Process Specialist Team to highlight and update any errors in procedures.

NIGHT MANAGER

DoubleTree by Hilton Dundee

March 2014 - June 2018

 Performing nightly audit cross checking and analysing all transactions across multiple POS systems, ensuring a financial balance for the business day.

PERSONAL ACHIEVEMENTS

- Nominated as "Star of the Month" on three occasions whilst working as a Data Gatherer.
- Maintained a quality score of over 95% for the duration of my time with Virgin Money.
- As a result of quality and production, I was retained by Virgin Money until the "PPI Project" came to an end.

PERSONAL HOBBIES

- Rugby
- Running
- Munro Bagging
- Reading

REFERENCES

Available on request

- Updating and implementing strict standard procedures to ensure each task is performed to a high standard consistently.
- Four weekly performance reviews for new team members, ensuring action plans of improvement are implemented.
- Working alongside the Training Manager, creating training plans and workshops to ensure staff engagement.
- Participating in ongoing training workshops Positive Qualities to improve management skills, and understand training techniques.
- Working alongside other departments to ensure the guest experience is prioritised throughout their journey through the hotel.

CONFERENCE & EVENTS SUPERVISOR

DoubleTree by Hilton Dundee

December 2013- March 2014

- Ensuring that all conference and events run smoothly and efficiently on daily basis.
- Setting up all functions following function sheets identifying customer requirements
- Addressing issues and solving problems within the department.

EDUCATION HISTORY

CODE INSTITUTE

Diploma in Software Development - Accredited by the University of Napier, Edinburgh

December 2020 - Present

The course is compromised of four Milestone Projects

- User Centric Frontend Development Grade: Distinction
- Interactive Frontend Development Submitted: Awaiting results
- Backend Development Yet to submit
- Full Stack Frameworks with Django Yet to submit

UNIVERSITY OF DUNDEE

BSC Hons Innovative Product Design (2.2)

September 2009 - June 2013

- Presented with a problem statement and using best practice along with personal judgement to identify the appropriate response.
- Experience and develop skills in and out of the workshop, gain knowledge and understanding of many areas of design, including manufacturing and computer-aided design.
- Work as part of a team to create an environment whereby everybody could voice their views and thoughts.

ROYAL GRAMMAR SCHOOL NEWCASTLE

2002 - 2009

- 3 A-levels Art (A), Design & Technology (B), Geography (B)
- 10 GCSE's Grade A-B